justbeenpaid.net 2017-12-16

# JustBeenPaid.Net | JUST INVEST FOR A JUST PROFIT

**  1.1. In compliance with the Data Protection Act 1998, the following information relates to the processing by us of your personal data.  Please note that in this privacy policy, “we” or “us” refers to the UK Commission for Employment and Skills trading as JUSTBEENPAID.NET Investors in People.**

1.2. We are committed to complying with the provisions of the Data Protection Act 1998 and ensuring that the personal data we hold is processed fairly and lawfully.  This Privacy Statement has therefore been prepared to tell you about the way we collect information from you and what we do with that information. If any part of this statement changes, we will tell you via our homepage at http://justbeenpaid.net.

1.3.  If you have any questions about this statement or your personal information that we may collect from you, please contact us at info@justbeenpaid.net.

1.4. This Privacy Policy explains how we collect information from you when you visit or register to use the Site and how this information is then used. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully and re-visit this page from time to time to review any changes that may have been made.

1.5.  We are registered as a data controller in accordance with United Kingdom Data Protection Act 1998. We will process any personal information we collect about you in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998.

1.6. This Privacy Policy applies to you whether you use the Site as a casual browser or if you have registered with the Site.

**WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT, AND HOW IS THAT INFORMATION THEN USED?**

**Information collected when you browse the Site**

2.1. Your IP Address: like most websites, each time you visit the Site we automatically collect your IP address and the web page from which you came. We use this information to administer and optimise the Site for you and to diagnose problems with our Site. We use your IP address to help identify you and to gather broad demographic information about you.

2.2. We will not collect any personal information about you from your browsing of the Site unless you agree to collection and use of your personal data by providing that information to us.

**Information collected when you register to the Site or download a publication via a ‘Web form’**

2.3. When you register to the Site, you may be asked to submit personal information about yourself in order to register and/or upload Content. This information may include, for example, your name, address, job title, telephone number, fax number, email address and postal address. We will only collect information that is necessary for us to allow you to upload Content and for us to provide you with any services or assistance connected with that Content.

**HOW WILL WE USE ANY PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT?**

2.4.  Where we collect personal information, we will use it for administration and to tailor our service and/or products to match your needs. We may also use personal information to conduct market research surveys, for statistical analysis to determine Site usage, to run competitions (and for direct marketing purposes relating to our business).

2.5. We may employ the services of a third party to help us in certain areas, such as delivery of IIP services ("Delivery Centres"), site or CRM hosting, marketing and market researching. In some cases that third party may receive your information. However, at all times we will control and be responsible for the use of your information.

2.6 We work closely with our appointed Investors in People “Delivery Centres” in the UK and internationally that cover defined territories. Information shared with us, unless specified otherwise, will also be shared with our appointed partner in the territory relevant to the business address postcode provided by you. From time to time “Delivery Centres” may change. If your data is being transferred we will notify you, and give you the opportunity to opt out of having your data transferred to the new partner, in advance of the migration taking place. UKCES remains the data controller in all cases. Our appointed "Delivery Centres" will use this data to: contact you, support you in maintaining or obtaining an IIP accreditation, working with the IIP Standard, provide updates back to us (UKCES) as data controller, refer you to other services or products that may be of benefit to you, introduce you to other businesses like yours and introduce offers from appropriate sponsors to you. To opt out of any communications please contact info@justbeenpaid.net.

2.7. At all times we are legally obliged to collect, retain and process any personal information that you provide in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998. Each time you provide us with personal information we aim to let you know how we intend to use it and ask you to give your consent to such use.  This will include (i) where we would like to use that information to send you details of other products and services we offer which are similar to the product/service for which you have subscribed; and   
(ii) where we would like to share that information with certain selected third parties to allow them to provide you with details of their services and/or products which might be of interest to you.

2.8. Your Personal Information may be shared with a third party in the event of a transfer of ownership, transfer of "Delivery Centre", assets or a bankruptcy of the UK Commission for Employment and Skills and/or Investors in People. We may also disclose your Personal Information as required or permitted by law, to protect the interests or safety of the UK Commission for Employment and Skills, http://justbeenpaid.net/ or a third party, or to prevent an emergency. Any third party with whom we share your Personal Information is authorised to use your Personal Information in accordance with our contractual arrangements with such third parties and in accordance with their own privacy policies, over which we have no control. Those who contact you will need to be instructed directly by you regarding your preferences for the use of your Personal Information by them.

**How can I remove, update, prevent use of or correct my personal information?**  
2.9. Please refer to the “My Dashboard” section of the Site where you can update, correct or delete your personal information as appropriate.  Should you wish us to change your contact preferences, you should also go to “My Dashboard” or contact info@justbeenpaid.net to be removed from our lists.

**HOW DO WE PROTECT YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?**

3.1. We will hold your personal information securely and will only keep it for as long as is reasonably necessary in the circumstances, or whilst you are registered to use the Site, unless you have provided us with your consent to use the data for any additional purposes.  We take the security of the Site and the information you provide very seriously and we will take all appropriate technical measures using recognised security procedures and tools in accordance with good industry practice to protect your personal information.

3.2. Whilst we use all reasonable endeavours to protect your security in the manner described above, we consider that it is only appropriate to advise users that data transmission over the Internet and the World Wide Web cannot always be guaranteed as 100% secure, and therefore that you use the Site at your own risk. Accordingly, we assume no liability for any disclosure of data due to errors in transmission, unauthorised third party access or other acts of third parties, or acts or omissions beyond our reasonable control.

**OUR COOKIE POLICY**

4.1. When we provide services, we want to make them easy, useful and reliable. Where services are delivered on the internet, this sometimes involves placing small amounts of information on your device, for example, computer or mobile phone. These include small files known as cookies.

**These pieces of information are used to improve services for you through, for example:**

·          enabling a service to recognise your device so you don't have to give the same information several times during one task

·          recognising that you may already have given a username and password so you don't need to do it for every web page requested

·          measuring how many people are using services, so they can be made easier to use and there's enough capacity to ensure they are fast

4.2 The majority of browsers will allow you to alter the settings used for cookies and to disable and enable them as you require.  If you do not want cookies then please refer to the “Help” menu on your browser for instructions on disabling them.  You can manage these small files yourself and learn more about them through "[Internet browser cookies - what they are and how to manage them](http://www.direct.gov.uk/managingcookies)"

**4.3. Our use of cookies**

4.3.1 Cookies for improving service

We use a Customer Relationship Management service called “Click Dimensions”. This system sets cookies in your browser to enable us to understand user behaviour, improve our service and provide users with more relevant information.  Click Dimensions uses three cookies:

Name: **cuvid**  
This cookie is typically written to the browser upon the first visit to the site  _from  that web browser_. If the cookie has been deleted by the browser operator, and the browser subsequently visits the site, a new __cuid cookie is written with a different visitor unique ID. This cookie is used to determine unique visitors to the site and it is updated with each page view. Additionally, this cookie is provided with a unique ID that the application uses to ensure both the validity and accessibility of the cookie as an extra security measure. This cookie expires 2 years from set/update.

Name: **cusid**

This cookie is used to establish and continue a user session with the site. When a user views a page on the site, the script code attempts to update this cookie. If it does not find the cookie, a new one is written and a new session is established. Each time a user visits a different page on the site, this cookie is updated to expire in 30 minutes, thus continuing a single session for as long as user activity continues within 30-minute intervals. This cookie expires when a user pauses on a page on the site for longer than 30 minutes. This cookie expires 30 minutes from set/update.

Name: **cuvon**  
Used to signal the last time a visitor viewed a page. This cookie expires 30 minutes from set/update.

For more information about Click Dimensions [please visit their website.](http://help.clickdimensions.com/clickdimensions-cookies-for-web-analytics/)

We also use a service called “Google Analytics” to understand user behaviour at different times of the day. Google Analytics sets cookies to help us more accurately estimate the number of visitors to the website and volumes of usage. This is to ensure that the service is available when you want it and fast. We use the following cookies on this site:

Name: _utma  
Typical content: randomly generated number.   
Expires: 2 years  
Name: _utmb  
Typical content: randomly generated number  
Expires: 30 mins  
Name: _utmc  
Typical content: randomly generated number  
Expires: when user exits browser  
Name: _utmv  
Typical content: Custom variable cookie used for tracking through the shop  
Expires: when user exits browser  
Name: _utmz  
Typical content: randomly generated number + info on how the site was reached (e.g. directly or via a link, organic search or paid search)  
Expires: 6 months

For further details on the cookies set by Google Analytics please refer to the [Google code website](http://code.google.com/apis/analytics/docs/concepts/gaConceptsCookies.html#cookiesSet).

4.3.2 Cookies to make site specific web services work

Name: loadedTT  
Typical content: randomly generated number used for the talk to speak service on the site.  
Expires: 89 years

Name: ASP.NET_SessionId  
Typical content: randomly generated alphanumeric  
Expires: when user session ends

4.4. Third parties advertisers on the Site may also place cookies on your browser. We will notify you of this when you attempt to access such an area. Once you have closed your browser, the cookie is deactivated.

**CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY**

5.1. If we make any changes to this Privacy Policy these changes will be detailed on this page in order to ensure that you are fully aware of what information is collected, how it is used and under what circumstances it will be disclosed.

**SCOPE**

6.1. This Privacy Policy applies to information collected by this Site and personal information gathered by our network of "Delivery Centres" and held in our national CRM database and associated databases.
